It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
어지러운 전국 시대.
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
Musashi is here-dasu!
무사시 등장이오!
Karakuri Kengouden
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
A man always dreams of the day
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
in the center of the world to become
제일 강해질 날을
AH! AH! the strongest
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
모험의 길의 막을 연다
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
Go! Fight!
가라! 싸워라!
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
Tomorrow will be glorious
내일은 빛난다
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Fight the utmost with the stillness
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
His eyes shined! Musashi!
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
For Kojirō, whose beloved sword was broken, Musashi heads to Amakusa Island, but he gets caught by Ikazuchi.
애도가 부러져 침울해진 코지로를 위해 무사시는 아마쿠사 섬에 향하지만 이카즈치에게 잡히고 만다.
But Kojirō obtained the legendary secret sword, Hououmaru, and used its great power to take down Ikazuchi.
그렇지만 코지로는 전설의 비검, 봉황환을 손에 넣어 그 대단한 힘으로 이카즈치를 쓰러트렸다.
What?!
어라?!
Musashi Dies
무사시는 죽소
What? You mean, our weapon factory in Amakusa Island?
뭐라? 아마쿠사 섬의 우리 무기 공장이?
Yes. Musashi, Kojirō, and Senhime's group came and done it.
예. 무사시, 코지로, 센히메 일행이 사이고를 데리고 와서 했습니다.
Musashi, eh...
무사시인가...
That's why I advised you to take care of them as soon as possible.
그러니까 충고했습니다. 놈들은 어서 처리하는 게 좋다고.
Hmph. I thought he was a simple child.
흥, 단순하게 아이일 뿐이라 생각했더니.
This happens because they're making poker faces.
놈들이 시치미를 떼고 있으니 이렇게.
Well, don't worry about that. We, Shiranui Clan do not get taken over by those small bunch.
뭐, 안심하세요. 그런 패거리에게 끌려다닐 시라누이 일족이 아닙니다.
Osenchan, wait for me-dasu!
오센짱, 같이 가오!
Hmph! Really!
흥! 정말 진짜!
Why are you angry at me-dasu?
왜 화내오...
Do you even know that we were in dire crisis just because you were acting on your own?!
맨날맨날 네 멋대로 행동만 해서 엄청 위험에 처했던 건 알고 있어?
Our lives should already have been exhausted by now!
원래라면 목숨이 몇개고 있어도 부족했어!
I'm sorry-dasu...
미안하오...
We might have been died!
보통이라면 죽었을 거야!
Yeah...
그렇소...
You only think about yourself, but never worries about everyone else!
자기 생각만 하고, 남 걱정은 안 하냐?
That's why I'm keeping to apologize-dasu!
그러니까, 계속 사과하오!
Hmph! Are you actually reflecting?
흥! 정말 반성하고 있냐?
I am-dasu.
하고 있소.
Then show me by actions.
그럼 태도로 증명해 봐.
By actions-dasu?
태도이오?
The first action of reflection.
반성 태도 제 1.
The second.
제 2.
SORRY
미안
The third.
제 3.
The fourth.
제 4.
The fifth.
제 5.
The sixth.
제 6.
The seventh.
제 7.
Musashi!
무사시!
Stop right there, Musashi!
멈춰, 무사시!
You're getting decapitated! I can't forgive you!
참수다! 너 따위 용서 못 해!
-Musashi! -Please forgive me-dasu!
-무사시! -봐 주시오!
You'll suffer this!
이렇게 해 주마!
That's Mr. Jūbee!
저건 주베 님.
Jūbee?
주베가?
Did you find something about Shiranui Clan?
시라누이 일족에 대해 뭔가 알았어?
Yessir.
예.
It seems that Shiranui Clan has their base somewhere in Unzen Mountain.
보아하니 시라누이 일족은 이 운젠 산의 어딘가에 본거지를 두고 있는 것 같습니다.
Mt. Unzen?
운젠 산?
Please be careful, Senhime.
센히메 님도 충분히 조심해 주십시오.
Got it.
예.
Mt. Unzen, is it-dasu...
운젠 산이오...
Musashi! Where are you going?
무사시! 어디 가?
To pee-dasu.
오줌이오.
Do you remember?
알고 있지?
Yes, of course! I have to restrain myself-dasu!
그렇소! 행동은 자중하오!
You don't have to do that-dasu...
그렇게까지 할 필요는 없소만...
No way! You might go somewhere!
안 돼! 어디에 갈 지 몰라!
Senhime.
센히메 님.
He's taking too much time.
시간이 너무 걸리잖아.
Musashi! How long does it take for you to pee?!
무사시! 언제까지 쉬하고 있을 거야!
A boar!
멧돼지다!
Senhime! Wait for me!
센히메 님! 같이 가요!
Kojirō! Do something!
코지로! 어떻게 좀 해 봐!
Leave it to me, Senhime!
맡겨 주세요, 센히메 님!
Ganryu Mister Kojirō will face you!
간류 미스터 코지로가 상대하겠다!
Yeah, face me!
그래, 덤벼 봐라!
Secret sword, Tsubamegaeshi!
비검! 츠바메가에시!
Kojirō! Don't kill them, as they're poor!
코지로! 불쌍하니까 죽이면 안 돼!
What?!
어?
As soon as I find out where Shiranui Clan's base is, they're mine-dasu!
시라누이 일족의 본거지만 알면 내 것이오!
I'll attack first this time, and clear my bad reputatoin-dasu!
이번에야말로 먼저 공격을 걸어서 오명을 만회하겠소!
Osenchan will reevaluate me, too-dasu!
오센짱도 날 다시 볼 것이오!
That damn Musashi!
진짜! 정말 무사시 놈!
He's unforgivable! Let's make him disembowel himself!
놈은 용서할 수 없습니다! 할복하게 만듭시다!
Disembowel! Disembowel! Decapitate! Execute! Disembowel!
할복이야, 할복이야! 참수야, 사형이야, 할복!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
T- this is my grandmother's bells. She told me that when these bells split into two, something bad will happen.
이, 이건 할머니 유품인 방울이야. 할머니가 말했어. 이 방울이 둘로 갈라지면 불길한 일이 일어날 거라고.
Seeing all those ill omens at once, I have a terrible foreboding...
이만큼 쌓인 걸 보니 엄청 나쁜 예감이 들어...
That does not work against me!
내게 그런 건 안 먹힌다!
That worked, though!
그건 좀 먹히는군!
Are you alright, Benkei?!
괜찮나, 벤케이!
Ushiwaka! I'm sorry! I let myself go easy!
우시와카 님! 죄송합니다! 제가 정신을 좀 놨습니다!
A battle is a real fight with real swords. One opening can be fatal.
전투는 진검 승부. 한순간의 틈이 생명을 좌우합니다.
Understood!
알겠습니다!
It seems that it's won't work favorably to us at this rate. Let's finish this at once!
보아하니 이대로는 우리가 불리합니다. 한번에 끝장냅시다!
Yessir!
예!
Tengu Style Fan Dance!
텐구류 부채춤!
You aren't defeating me and Ushiwaka!
어차피 나와 우시와카 님에게는 못 당해낼 테다!
Impudent bastards!
건방진 놈들.
You!
너는!
Genba of Lava
용암의 겐바
Everyone recognizes me, Genba, just by Mt. Unzen!
운젠 산이라고 하면 더 말할 것도 없이 다 아는 겐바 님이시다.
I'll show you what it means to stand in the way of Shiranui Clan!
시라누이 일족을 막아서면 어떻게 되는지 알려주마!
Ushiwaka! Leave this to me!
우시와카 님! 여긴 제게 맡기쇼!
Benkei. I will do so.
후후, 벤케이. 맡깁니다.
Shiranui magic, Lava Shell!
시라누이 요술 용암탄!
Benkei!
벤케이!
As long as evil exists in this world, my mission is to exterminate them!
이 세상에 악이 있는 한 퇴치하는 것이 나의 사명!
I'll show you the difference of the swords of Niten'ichiryū-dasu!
이천일류의 검의 차이를 보여 주겠소!
Mr. Ushiwaka! Mr. Benkei! It's been a while-dasu!
우시와카 씨! 벤케이 씨! 오랜만이오! 일만 냥 무예 대회에서의 은혜를 갚아 드리겠소!
Thank you. We're entrusting it on you.
그건 고맙습니다. 맡기겠습니다.
Musashi! Be careful of what he throws!
무사시! 그 놈이 던지는 거 조심해라!
Understood-dasu!
알겠소!
Divide steel helmet into two with one strike!
일격에 둘로 철모 나누기!
Musashi!
무사시!
Musashi.
무사시.
(Mushi: Bug)
(무시: 벌레)
Musashi has flown into the flame.
날아서 불에 뛰어드는 여름의 무사시인가.
It hurts! Mommy!
아파, 아파! 엄마!
-Mommy! -What's wrong, Musashi?
-엄마! -왜 그러니, 무사시?
I fell down.
나, 넘어졌어.
That must've hurt! Pain, pain, go away!
저런, 아팠겠다. 엄마 손은 약손이지?
Look! You're fine now!
자! 이제 괜찮지?
Yeah, I'm good now!
응, 이제 안 아퍼.
Mommy...
엄마...
Mommy!
엄마!
It was a dream...
꿈이오...
Mr. Musashi? Did you wake up?
무사시 씨? 일어나셨나요?
Mommy...
엄마...
No, Mr. Musashi!
안 돼요, 무사시 씨.
What could be Himiko up to? Wait for the stormy latter half!
히미코의 속셈은 무엇인가? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Excuse me. I'd like to ask you if you see a Karakuri martial artist who's very gluttonous and half-witted?
실례합니다. 묻고 싶은게 있습니다만, 몹시 게걸스럽고 얼빠진 얼굴을 한 카라쿠리 무예가를 보셨습니까?
No.
아니.
Did you see a weirdo with a big head and short legs who shouts I'm hungry-dasu! around?
머리 크고, 다리 짧고, 나 배고프오! 이라던가 멍청하게 말하는 이상한 사람 못 봤어요?
I don't know.
몰라요.
I've asked all Dango or Satsumaage house around here, but it seems that nobody saw him.
이 주변에 있는 단고집이나 사츠마아게집에는 죄다 물어봤습니다만 무사시를 봤다는 사람은 아무도 없습니다.
That's it!
그거야!
Doyou have a good idea?
뭔가 좋은 아이디어가?
Let's try finding by drawing a portrait!
초상화를 그려서 찾아 보자!
P- portrait?!
초, 초상화!?
Did you do it?
됐어?
No, I- I'm not ready yet.
아니, 아, 아직입니다.
It's alright! Show me!
괜찮잖아, 보여줘!
Well, that's, kinda...
어, 그게, 좀...
What's this?
뭐야, 이거.
Err, drawing was not my best when I was young...
음, 저, 어릴 적부터 그림 잘 못 그렸으니...
Now our only hope is you, Senhime!
이제 센히메 님께 기대하는 수밖에 없습니다!
Uh, no, I'm not ready too.
아, 싫어, 나도 좀...
I only read girl comics since I was a child, and thus this is the only kind of drawing I can draw.
나, 어린이일 때부터 소녀 만화만 읽어서 이런 그림밖에 못 그려.
The reason we're being reminded of bad memories is also Musashi's fault!
이런 기분 나쁜 기억을 하는 것도 전부 무사시 탓입니다!
He'll be decapitated when we get him!
찾아내면 참수시킬 거야!
Mr. Benkei and Mr. Ushiwaka!
벤케이 님에 우시와카 님!
What? Musashi did?!
어? 무사시가?
Yes. With serious injuries.
예. 꽤 상처를 입어서.
When we went down the cliff, we couldn't see his form or shadow.
우리가 절벽 아래로 내려갔을 때는 모습도 그림자도 없었쇼.
If he's really that injured, he shouldn't be far away.
그렇게 상처를 입었다면 멀리 갔을 리가 없다.
How do we not know when we were with him...
무슨 일이 있던 것인지... 우리가 곁에 있으면서...
It all happened in Mt. Unzen.
운젠 산에서 일어난 일이라는 거지.
-Kojirō! -Got it. Right away.
-코지로! -네. 즉시.
I hope my bad foreboding is wrong...
나쁜 예감이 맞지 않으면 좋겠는데...
It's tasty!
맛있소.
Really, you saved me-dasu, Ms. Himiko!
정말 나 히미코 씨가 구해줘서 살았소!
-Open. -Ahh.
-자. -아.
It tastes even great, maybe because you're so kind-dasu, Ms. Himiko!
밥도 히미코 씨가 상냥해서인지 더 맛있소.
Hey, it's empty already. Mr. Musashi, do you want to have more?
어라, 벌써 텅 비었네요. 무사시 씨, 더 먹을래요?
Yes-dasu! I'll eat more-dasu!
그렇소! 더 먹소!
Please wait for a moment.
잠깐만 기다려 주세요.
Tell Genba to be prepared.
준비해 두라고 겐바에게 전해라.
Ms. Himiko!
히미코 씨!
Y- yeah!
아, 예!
Excuse me-dasu. Where's the toilet-dasu?
실례하오. 화장실 어디이오?
Yes, I'll take you to there.
네, 네, 제가 데려가 드릴게요.
Being like this feels like I'm with my mother-dasu!
정말, 이러고 있으니 나 엄마하고 있는 것 같소!
Am I really that like your mother, Mr. Musashi?
제가 그렇게 무사시 씨의 어머님과 닮았나요?
Well, I have never met my mother-dasu.
아니, 나, 엄마하고 본 적 없소.
Hm?
음?
When I woke up, I was alone-dasu...
정신이 드니, 혼자였소...
I see.
그렇군요.
If she exists, then I guess that she's just like you, Ms. Himiko!
만약 있다면, 분명 히미코 씨 같지 않을까 하오.
I feel great-dasu. It really worth it to come to Unzen-dasu!
좋은 기분이오. 운젠까지 온 보람이 있었소!
Right-dasu! Shiranui's base is at here, Unzen-dasu!
그렇소! 이 운젠은 시라누이 일족의 본거지가 있소!
What? Shiranui Clan? Well, that's scary!
어? 시라누이 일족? 음, 그건 무섭네요.
Ms. Himiko, you shouldn't be at a place like this-dasu. Go to somewhere safer-dasu!
히미코 씨, 이런 곳에 있으면 안 되오. 더 안전한 곳에!
(Jigokudani: lit. Hell Valley)
(지고쿠다니: 지옥곡)
Erm, I came here because I heard that there is a famous place called Jigokudani where lava sprouts,
예, 여기에 온 건 지고쿠다니라고 하는 용암이 분출하는 명소가 있어, 거기에 기도하면 소원이 이루어진대서...
Let's go see that place together! And then we'll get off Mt. Unzen.
함께 뵈러 가요! 그리고 둘이서 운젠에서 내려가면 되겠지요?
That's a good idea-dasu!
그건 좋은 생각이오!
Good job, Kerokichi! It's been 80 years since I fed this frog!
네, 케로키치, 수고했어! 전 개구리를 먹여온 지 80년째입니다! 이젠 대화도 가능해요!
He says that today's audiences were excellent!
오늘의 손님들은 좋은 손님들이었다고 하네요!
Now, let me introduce the result of my 79 years of research: Toad Oil!
그럼 이 제가 79년의 연구 끝에 만들어 낸 것이, 이 두꺼비 기름!
Yes, this Toad Oil is completely different from your everyday toad oils!
그래요, 이게 그 근방에 있는 다른 두꺼비 기름과는 다릅니다.
It is specially taken from toads full of warts!
사마귀 가득한 두꺼비에게서 골라낸 것입니다.
Look! First, put mirror in every direction around that toad with warts!
자, 모이신 여러분! 사마귀 주변에 사방으로 거울을 둡니다! 그럼 두꺼비는 자신의 모습의 추함에 주르륵 주르륵 하고 기름을 흘립니다.
And by collecing that, we can get Toad Oil like this!
그걸 모으면 이렇게 두꺼비 기름이 짜자잔! 하고 나옵니다!
Awesome!
대단해!
Hey, there, granny! You look like you'd sweat oil too if you see mirrors!
아, 거기, 할머니. 거울 보면 할머니도 기름땀 흘릴 것 같으시군요.
What?!
뭐?!
Well then, again, Everyone! Huh?
자, 그럼, 다시, 여러분! 어?
I- it's Musashi!
무, 무사시다!
Who is that woman? She is too pretty for Musashi to take.
저 여성은 누구지? 무사시가 데리고 다니기에는 너무 예뻐.
Moreover, that way is to Jigokudani.
게다가 저긴 지고쿠다니 방향.
-Hey! -What are you doing?!
-어이! -뭐 하고 있어!
Oh, right, right, right! This Toad Oil is usually 100 mons, but for today only, it's 50 mons!
아, 네, 네, 네! 자, 그럼 이 두꺼비 기름, 평소라면 100문이지만, 오늘은 더 깎아서 50문입니다!
Jigokudani
지고쿠다니
It's amazing-dasu! I never saw something like this-dasu!
대단하오. 이런 건 처음 보오!
Mr. Musashi, are you scared?
무사시 씨, 무서워요?
No, it's nothing more than a prowess of a Karakuri martial artist-dasu!
아니, 카라쿠리 무예가가 이런 걸로! 단지 무사다운 거동이오!
Then let's pray.
자, 기도해요.
Right-dasu.
그렇소.
To take down General Ieyasu, and for Shiranui Clan to take over the whole country.
내가 제너럴 이에야스를 무너트리고 시라누이 일족의 천하가 올 수 있도록.
To become the number one martial artist of Jipangu, and to take care of Shiranui Clan.
지팡구 제일의 무예가가 될 수 있도록, 그리고, 시라누이 일족을 퇴치할 수 있도록.
Even further, to eat enough whenever I want so that I can feel full, like dumplings, dorayaki, and...
그걸 넘어서, 언제라도 배 가득 먹을 수 있도록. 만두라던가, 팥과자라던가, 또...
Fall!
떨어져라!
Hmph, that was a nice evasion. But you're really going down this time!
흥, 잘 피했군. 그러나 이번엔 끝장이다!
You're that guy from before! I'm not letting my guard down this time-dasu!
저놈은 그때 그놈! 이번엔 방심 안 하오!
I won't let you even lay your finger on Ms. Himiko, risking the pride of a martial artist-dasu!
히미코 씨에게는 무예가의 고집을 걸고 손가락 하나 못 대게 하갰소!
Oh, is that so? How interesting.
그러냐. 재밌네.
Ms. Himiko, run away right now-dasu! I'll stop him no matter what-dasu!
히미코 씨, 지금 달아나시오! 내가 막아 보이겠소!
Mr. Musashi!
무사시 씨!
He has my pity, but it won't stop this. Finish him, Genba.
가엾지만 상관 없다. 잘 끝내라, 겐바.
It's end for you, Musashi!
끝이구나, 무사시!
Shiranui Magic, Lava Shell!
시라누이 요술 용암탄!
-Mr. Jūbee! -Mr. Musashi. Leave this to me.
-주베 씨! -무사시 님. 여긴 제게 맡겨 주세요.
-You may come! -Hmph! No matter the enemy, I don't care!
-자, 와라! -흥, 상대가 누구라도 난 상관 없다!
Musashi!
무사시!
-Where are you?! -Musashi!
-어디 있어! -무사시!
Excuse me.
어, 저기, 거기 행인님.
What is it?
네, 뭔 일이라도?
We're looking for someone called Musashi; do you know him?
무사시라는 자를 찾고 있습니다만 알고 계십니까?
Well, Musashi... I think I heard that name before.
자, 무사시라... 어디서 들은 거 같은 이름이다만...
-He eats a lot. -He's so vulgar.
-많이 먹고, -품위 없고,
-He says I am Musashi-dasu! -He's a short-legged martial artist.
-나, 무사시이오! 하고 말하는 -다리 짧은 무예가이오.
Oh, I remembered him. He went towards Jigokudani.
아, 기억났습니다. 그 분이라면 지고쿠다니 쪽으로 갔어요.
To Jigokudani? Thanks!
지고쿠다니에? 고마워요!
Could you possibly be Jiraiyan?
혹시 그쪽은 지라이얀이?
N- no, that's not true!
아, 아니, 그럴 리 없습니다!
Oh, is that so? Then excuse me.
아, 그렇습니까. 그럼 실례합니다.
Those guys are really annoying.
저 놈들, 정말 귀찮게 하는 놈들이야.
Yagyū Shinkage Style, Tailwind Long Sword!
야규신카게류 순풍의 대도!
Without your spear, you're over!
창이 없으면 끝장이겠다!
I still have this!
아직 이게 있다!
Mr. Jūbee, watch out!
주베 씨, 조심하시오!
Mr. Jūbee!
주베 씨!
Time to finish this!
끝장이다!
Stop!
멈춰라!
Shiranui! We'll face you from now on!
시라누이! 여긴 우리가 상대해 주겠다!
Musashi! I was worried about you!
무사시! 걱정했어!
I'm sorry-dasu. I thought it was over this time-dasu.
미안하오. 이번엔 틀렸다고 생각했소.
Take this!
먹어라!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Osenchan, watch out!
오센짱, 위험하오!
Musashi!
무사시!
A hero of justice never dies no matter what-dasu!
정의의 히로는 어떤 일이 있어도 안 죽소!
That's death for you.
아미타불이다.
Musashi!
무사시!
Musashi from Miyamoto village has died. His final moment was too short.
미야모토 마을의 무사시는 죽었다. 너무나도 어이없는 최후였다. 카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드의 주인공은 죽고 말았다.
Where is this story going to? Let's wait for the most fantastic next story!
대체 이 이야기는 어디로 흘러가는가? 기상천외한 다음 이야기를 기다리자!
Sometimes the moon jumps over
허공의 주머니에 달이
the pocket of empty sky
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
Laugh loudly and
큰 소리로 웃으면
morning will come tomorrow
내일에는 아침이 와
Don't worry too much about losing
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Keep going! Go for it!
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
A bare hand is strong
맨손은 강해
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how life is! Look, a chance
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
follows us wagging its tail!
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
The spiritual world has finally called me-dasu. I died and that couldn't be helped-dasu!
찾아온 대영계. 아, 역시 난 죽고 말았소.
Still, I met Mr. Ishimatsu in a while! Good enough!
그래도, 그리웠던 이시마츠 씨하고 만났으니 뭐, 됐소!
In the spiritual world where Shuten and Onihime are being self-indulgent, I make great activities!
슈텐하고 오니히메가 멋대로 설치는 영계에서 나는 대활약하오.
But I have to go back to Sanzu River in order to revive!
그러나 살아 돌아가기 위해선 어서 삼도내로 돌아가야!
Next story! Of Course! Musashi is Immortal
다음 이야기! 역시 불사신 무사시이오
It's a stormy great spiritual world-dasu!
질풍노도의 대영계이오!
Next Episode
다음 이야기
Of Course!
역시 불사신
Musashi is Immortal
무사시이오
Look forwards for it!
기대하세요!